Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Studio Portraits (Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref362; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 19 August 1964; ref363; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 2 March 1971; ref364; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A studio portrait of a boy that has been drawn on., 1969; ref365; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 3.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy that has been drawn on., Circa 1955-1975; ref366; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref367; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.6 x 6.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a leather jacket., 1970; ref368; Cairo Studio, Ahmed Hariri, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a baby being held up by an adult., 1968; ref369; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a plaid shirt., 15 May 1969; ref370; Studio Egypt, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref371; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a leather jacket., 17 February 1972; ref372; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.1 x 4.9 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref373; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.1 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy that has been drawn on., 24 April 1967; ref374; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a tweed jacket., Circa 1955-1975; ref375; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref376; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref377; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 3.7 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 4 January 1963; ref378; Photo Lox, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., 3 July 1970; ref379; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref380; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a striped sweater., Circa 1955-1975; ref381; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a plaid collar., Circa 1955-1975; ref382; Studio Haig, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a plaid shirt., Circa 1955-1975; ref383; Studio Echbelia, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.8 x 5.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Calligraphy; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref384; Studio Al-Babk, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 x 5.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref385; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 x 5.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref386; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., 12 March 1970; ref387; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 6.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref388; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref389; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 x 3.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Children; Boys; Studio Photography; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a plaid shirt., 21 September 1964; ref390; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a tie and a sweater vest., Circa 1955-1975; ref391; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 5.6 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a plaid shirt., 26 December 1959; ref392; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a boy., September 1953; ref393; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Arabic Writing; Damascus, Syria; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a tie., Circa 1955-1975; ref394; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Arabic Writing; Syria; Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref395; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Men; Syria; Facial Hair; Arabic Calligraphy; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref396; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., December 1969; ref398; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., December 1970; ref399; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref400; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 12 April 1971; ref401; Studio Zenobia, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.6 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref402; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 11 July 1970; ref403; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref404; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., 1972; ref405; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 3.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a turtleneck., 1972; ref406; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 3.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a sweater., 8 February 1972; ref407; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 8.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref408; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref409; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., 27 August 1971; ref410; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 3.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A studio portrait of a man., 17 July 1972; ref411; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1955-1975; ref412; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref413; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., 20 December 1963; ref414; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Facial Hair; Men; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref415; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - A studio portrait of a man in a striped suit., 15 March 1966; ref416; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., 8 December 1971; ref417; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref418; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref419; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1955-1975; ref420; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Men; Syria; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref421; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man., February 1972; ref422; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Men; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., 1950; ref423; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 x 3.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a patterned shirt., Circa 1955-1975; ref424; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 20 December 1969; ref425; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a military uniform., 15 February 1972; ref426; Studio Al-Kindi, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.6 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a military uniform and a cap., 19 July 1972; ref427; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Studio Photography; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a military uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref428; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.1 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a man in a suit., 13 May 1971; ref429; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.1 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Men; Studio Photography; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1955-1975; ref430; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Men; Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., 1957; ref431; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 3.8 x 3.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - A studio portrait of a man with mustache., 9 September 1957; ref432; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform., 1953; ref433; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache in uniform., 9 March 1970; ref434; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Men; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a uniform and a cap., Circa 1955-1975; ref435; Studio Al-Rabih, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Arabic Writing; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military/Soldiers
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a military uniform and a cap., Circa 1955-1975; ref436; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 6.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Men; Uniforms; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache in uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref437; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Men; Uniforms; Facial Hair; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man., 1957; ref438; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Men; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a young man., March 1971; ref439; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache in uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref440; Studio Karwan, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.1 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Men; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache in uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref441; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache in uniform., 19 March 1975; ref442; Hassen Yazil, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Men; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Studio Photography; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache in uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref443; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform., 19 September 1970; ref444; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Facial Hair; Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache in uniform., 26 January 1967; ref445; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Men; Uniforms; Syria; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref446; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Uniforms; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref447; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform., 21 May 1973; ref448; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Men; Uniforms; Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform wearing a cap., 22 May 1963; ref449; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5 x 3.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Uniforms; Men; Military/Soldiers; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform wearing a cap., Circa 1955-1975; ref450; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Men; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of a man in uniform wearing a cap., 15 July 1971; ref451; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref452; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 22 December 1971; ref453; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.2 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref454; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1971; ref455; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.8 x 3.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref456; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref457; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 14 February 1971; ref458; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 3.4 x 2.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref459; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 2 June 1970; ref460; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref461; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - A studio portrait of a woman wearing a headscarf., 12 June 1965; ref462; Studio Vense, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Head Covers/Veils; Women; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a girl., Circa 1955-1975; ref463; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Girls; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a girl., Circa 1955-1975; ref464; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Girls; Women; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a young woman with her hair tied up., Circa 1955-1975; ref465; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Girls; Children; Jewelry; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women
  - A studio portrait of a woman with a floral blazer., Circa 1955-1975; ref466; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Women; Damascus, Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a woman with a choker smiling., Circa 1955-1975; ref467; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.2 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Women; Jewelry; Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a woman smiling and turned to the side., 16 January 1954; ref468; Studio Safar, Sanjakdar, Damas (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Women; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman with bangs wearing eyeliner., Circa 1955-1975; ref469; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Women; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman standing in front of a tree., Circa 1955-1975; ref470; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.1 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Women; Outdoors; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a woman wearing earrings., 1954; ref471; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 5.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)